<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sqvrltastic Art Archive</title><description>Hi, I'm sqvrltastic and I'm a digital artist. Welcome to my website! This is my main place for posting my artwork and sharing my thoughts.</description><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/rss.xml</link><atom:link href="https://sqvrltastic.art/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>1440</ttl><webMaster>sqvrltastic@gmail.com</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 UTC</lastBuildDate><language>en-us</language><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/fantasy-assassin.html</guid><title>Fantasy Assassin (Commission) [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/fantasy-assassin.jpg"/><p>Male dark fantasy assassin spellsword character. He is looking over his shoulder and is holding a sword in his right hand and his left hand is glowing with blue magical light as if readying a spell.</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/fantasy-assassin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="478245"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/fantasy-assassin.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>I updated the design of my website! Also, I removed the “enter” page, as well as the “contact” page and instead I fused it with the “home” page now. Also I added a few new links and new buttons for my website. Aaand I updated the home page and about me section a bit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>I finally purchased a custom domain (sqvrltastic.art) with Porkbun! 🥳🎉 I will keep the old free GitHub Pages domain working for a while as a fallback, but I will be replacing all my old links with the new ones and I encourage you to update any as well if you have any materials from my site linked, or if you are subscribed with RSS! This is my first time purchasing a domain so bear with me if I inadvertently break something!</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/drg-driller-scout-yaoi.html</guid><title>Driller x Scout yaoi [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/drg-driller-scout-yaoi.jpg"/><p>Driller and Scout are looking in each other's eyes in a romantic way. Driller is grinning and Scout is visibly flustered. Driller is holding a C4 satchel.</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/drg-driller-scout-yaoi.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="591060"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/drg-driller-scout-yaoi.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/montenegro-montenegro-redraw-of-the-dignitaries-selfie.html</guid><title>Redraw of the Montengrin dignitaries selfie [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/montenegro-redraw-of-the-dignitaries-selfie.jpg"/><p>Redraw of the Montengrin dignitaries selfie photo from Vatican. Featuring (from left to right): a man in a sunglasses smilling, a woman with seductive gaze, a man with a disturbed expression on his face and an old man with a tired expression.</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/montenegro-redraw-of-the-dignitaries-selfie.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="232556"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/montenegro-montenegro-redraw-of-the-dignitaries-selfie.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/drg-female-roughneck-driller-concept.html</guid><title>Deep Rock Galactic female roughneck driller dwarf concept [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/drg-female-roughneck-driller.jpg"/><p>A female dwarf is grinning and looking at the viewer while holding a colette wave cooker in her right hand. She is wearing standard driller armor, a protective cap and a fuel tank on her back. She has sideburns and a muscular body.</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/drg-female-roughneck-driller.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="824751"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/drg-female-roughneck-driller-concept.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>Added some new useful resource links in the “coding” and “art” links sections. Added a “skip to main” focusable skip link for accessibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/blog/i-wish-more-artists-had-a-personal-website.html</guid><title>I wish more artists had a personal website... [blog]</title><description>Rambly blog post about wishing for a more human, more enriching web for artists specifically.</description><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/blog/i-wish-more-artists-had-a-personal-website.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/vermintide-kerillian-with-a-chicken.html</guid><title>Kerillian with a chicken [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/vermintide-kerillian-with-a-chicken.jpg"/><p>elf Kerillian holding a chicken saying "The hell is that? That is just my chicken, Kruber", with Kruber in the background with a mortified expression on his face saying "By Taal..."</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/vermintide-kerillian-with-a-chicken.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="650083"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/vermintide-kerillian-with-a-chicken.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>Deleted and added some new links. Changed a bit the “buttons” page; also, I no longer allow hotlinking of my images. Added “artwork” and “blog” tags to RSS items so they are easier to filter out in case you want to. Implemented some minor code improvements regarding the way images are embedded on this website. All in all, nothing major, mostly just polishing work.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/lotgh-reinhard-portrait.html</guid><title>Reinhard portrait [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/lotgh-reinhard-portrait.jpg"/><p>Black and white pencil-style sketch portrait of Reinhard von Lohengramm</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/lotgh-reinhard-portrait.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="796841"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/lotgh-reinhard-portrait.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>Updated my “Full guide to RSS”; added a small section at the bottom about on how to make your RSS feed autodiscoverable. Additionally, added some cool new sites in the “links” section. Oh and, you can now find the HUGO source files of this website on my GitHub, if you ever wondered how I made this site the way I did.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>I completely remade the template for the RSS news feed and the site’s own updates feed. Well, mostly on the developer side, you yourself won’t see many differences. Basically I made a template in HUGO and automated it, whereas previously I would code it by hand, which was pretty tedious and prone to making mistakes. Make sure to clear your reader’s cache if you have any issues! Also, now every artwork has a small annotation below!</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/vermintide-kerillian-drinking-leaf-lovers.html</guid><title>Kerillian drinking Leaf Lover's Special beer [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/vermintide-kerillian-drinking-leaf-lovers.jpg"/><p>elf Kerillian drinking Leaf Lover's Special beer with an annoyed expression on her face</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/vermintide-kerillian-drinking-leaf-lovers.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="879239"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/vermintide-kerillian-drinking-leaf-lovers.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/vermintide-kerillian-thinking-face.html</guid><title>Thinking face Kerillian [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/vermintide-kerillian-thinking-face.jpg"/><p>elf Kerillian with a thinking expresion on her face</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/vermintide-kerillian-thinking-face.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="337638"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/vermintide-kerillian-thinking-face.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/vermintide-kerillian-smug-asuka.html</guid><title>Kerillian redraw as smug Asuka [artwork]</title><description><img src="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/vermintide-kerillian-smug-asuka.jpg"/><p>elf waystalker Kerillian looking smug</p></description><enclosure url="https://sqvrltastic.art/images/full/vermintide-kerillian-smug-asuka.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="237089"/><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/gallery/vermintide-kerillian-smug-asuka.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>Deleted two blog posts (I just didn’t like them, I feel like they were too low effort). Changed my whole gallery template in HUGO to make it fully automated. This shouldn’t affect anything too much for the end user though so you won’t see many changes. Fixed some broken links, changed some stuff, yada yada, the usual. Not worth mentioning here.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://sqvrltastic.art/blog/how-to-subscribe.html</guid><title>How to subscribe to this website — a guide [blog]</title><description>A guide on how to subscribe with RSS to Sqvrltastic Art Archive to get updates when I post new content or update this site.</description><link>https://sqvrltastic.art/blog/how-to-subscribe.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>My PC is still broken… (update: it’s fixed now). In the meantime, I rewrote and cleaned up a lot of CSS code on the website. For you this mostly means that there are some minor layout changes. Also, I added a big RSS feed button down in the footer section and a simple guide on how to subscribe to this website’s updates right there as well. So if you haven’t figured out how to do it already, hopefully how you will!</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Website update</title><description>Minor website CSS changes! Just trying to make this website easier on the eyes. Also, I kept the main font being monospace, but now it will show as whatever default monospace font you have in your browser, not as Courier New like before. Additionally, updated coding resources links and added “Images: figcaption vs alt. text” link under accessibility section.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>