<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Links on Sqvrltastic art archive</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/</link><description>Recent content in Links on Sqvrltastic art archive</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Art resources links dump</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/art-resources-links-dump.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/art-resources-links-dump.html</guid><description>Art resources links dump Last updated: January 30th 2025
Content warning for some mild artistic nudity in some links!
Proko YouTube channel — feel like this is one of the best free resources out there for learning figure drawing
PureRef — useful free little software for keeping and managing a reference board.
Skull Sketcher v2 — small program that lets you spin and light a 3D model of a skull, useful for anatomy drawing practice.</description></item><item><title>Coding resources links dump</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/coding-resources-links-dump.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/coding-resources-links-dump.html</guid><description>Coding resources links dump Last updated: February 13th 2025
MDN Web Docs — references and documentation on HTML, CSS and JavaScript; useful when you need to look up a particular tag or an attribute.
W3Schools — similar to abovementioned MDN; lots of documentation and tutorials.
ChatGPT — You don&amp;rsquo;t have to use it if you are against generative AI in all forms, but personally I think it can be helpful in supplementing your learning process.</description></item><item><title>My other projects</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/my-other-projects.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/my-other-projects.html</guid><description>
My other projects
Simple Recipes — a minimalist cooking website for the lazy
and easily distracted ones. Although, I treat it mostly as a personal
cooking scrapbook of sorts.</description></item><item><title>Random</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/random.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/random.html</guid><description>Random
Last updated: January 30th 2025
Just some cool stuff, useful and not really.
Wiby — search engine for old and indie websites.
Human-made web button — 88x31 web button by Ash Kyd. Used
to indicate that your content is not AI generated.
Adopt a censor panda — collection of website graphics for
displaying your website's age rating.</description></item><item><title>Useful software</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/useful-software.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/links/useful-software.html</guid><description>Useful software Last updated: January 30th 2025
Also, be sure to check coding resources links and art resources links for more software recommendations!
For desktop (Windows &amp;amp; Linux) Joplin — open source note-taking app.
qBittorent — my open source torrent client of choice.
Wintoys — I use this for some further Windows OS management.
PowerToys — some extra utility features for Windows desktop.
For Android F-Droid — installable app store of FOSS (Free and Open Source Software) applications for the Android platform.</description></item></channel></rss>