<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Sqvrltastic art archive</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Sqvrltastic art archive</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to subscribe to this website — a guide</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/how-to-subscribe.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/how-to-subscribe.html</guid><description>How to subscribe to this website — a guide Want to receive updates when I post new content? No need to sign up with email or create an account!
Here is how!👇️ Step 1 Download an RSS reader for your platform:
Windows &amp;amp; MacOS: Fluent Reader Linux: Newsflash Android: Feeder &amp;hellip; or any other RSS reader of your choice!
Step 2 Launch the app. Find a button that says something like: &amp;ldquo;add new feed&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;add new source&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Markdown cheat sheet</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/markdown-cheat-sheet.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/markdown-cheat-sheet.html</guid><description>Markdown cheat sheet
Last updated: January 31st 2025
Markdown is a lightweight markup language that lets you add formatting
elements to plaintext documents. It's used by a lot of
SSGs (like mine, HUGO), but also
in places like Discord and Reddit among others. Its main advantage is
readability and simple syntax.
Different implementations of Markdown vary a bit between software and
platforms. This guide is mostly from my own perspective and includes info
about features that I personally use the most.</description></item><item><title>Full guide to RSS</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/full-guide-to-rss.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/full-guide-to-rss.html</guid><description>Full guide to RSS
Last updated: January 21st 2025
Table of content
What is RSS?
Why use RSS?
For users: How to use RSS
For developers: How to add an RSS feed to your website
What is RSS?
From
Wikipedia:
"RSS (which stands for "Really Simple Syndication") is a web feed that
allows users and applications to access updates to websites in a
standardized, computer-readable format.</description></item><item><title>Please, stop posting your artwork to Twitter</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/stop-posting-artwork-to-twitter.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/stop-posting-artwork-to-twitter.html</guid><description>Please, stop posting your artwork to Twitter Yes, I know, it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; now. No, I don&amp;rsquo;t care. I will be calling it Twitter in this blog post. &amp;ldquo;Man, have you seen that tweet on X?&amp;rdquo;, said literally nobody. Also, why is it still called a &amp;ldquo;tweet&amp;rdquo;, if it&amp;rsquo;s on X? Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be called a xeet?.. I digress. Anyway&amp;hellip; Here is why you should delete and uninstall Twitter like, right now&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Neocities and the (misguided) idolization of the old web</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/idolization-of-the-old-web.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/idolization-of-the-old-web.html</guid><description>Neocities and the (misguided) idolization of the old web I get a feeling that a lot of Neocities users are teens, or at least born after 2005 and never really experienced the &amp;ldquo;old web&amp;rdquo; personally. I&amp;rsquo;m saying this because people really need to stop idolizing the &amp;ldquo;old web&amp;rdquo; so much.
This might seem hypocritical, after all, isn’t my own website kinda oldish looking? Yes and no. While I do like a lot of design trends from a bygone era and despise a lot of modern web development trends, I still do recognize that there are a lot of things that sucked about the web 1.</description></item><item><title>Plans for 2025 year</title><link>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/plans-for-2025-year.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sqvrltastic.github.io/blog/plans-for-2025-year.html</guid><description>Plans for 2025 year I don&amp;rsquo;t know why, but I keep struggling to get this website indexed by search engine crawler bots. Supposedly, it should be an automated process, but it just doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to work for me. I had to manually submit my page to Google for it to get it indexed, but it only worked with the landing page.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;hellip; To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m at a loss of what causes it, but I suspect that the issue might be with GitHub itself.</description></item></channel></rss>